{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128484786","data":{"timestamp":" 947128484786"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 83f37134-5f6d-4044-9d5f-8e406a428932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128530417","data":{"timestamp":" 947128530416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 83f37134-5f6d-4044-9d5f-8e406a428932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128530552","data":{"timestamp":" 947128530551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 83f37134-5f6d-4044-9d5f-8e406a428932"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128563838","data":{"timestamp":" 947128563837"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f824b62e-f6d6-4642-bcf2-52fca3967479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZIWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" ZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128566833","data":{"timestamp":" 947128566832"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f824b62e-f6d6-4642-bcf2-52fca3967479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZIWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" ZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128568453","data":{"timestamp":" 947128568452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f824b62e-f6d6-4642-bcf2-52fca3967479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZIPU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128570847","data":{"timestamp":" 947128570846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f824b62e-f6d6-4642-bcf2-52fca3967479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZIPU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128572476","data":{"timestamp":" 947128572475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f824b62e-f6d6-4642-bcf2-52fca3967479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZAIDI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128575094","data":{"timestamp":" 947128575092"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f824b62e-f6d6-4642-bcf2-52fca3967479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZAIDI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128576723","data":{"timestamp":" 947128576722"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f824b62e-f6d6-4642-bcf2-52fca3967479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZAWADI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAWADI"," userResponse":" ZAWADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128579676","data":{"timestamp":" 947128579676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f824b62e-f6d6-4642-bcf2-52fca3967479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZAWADI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAWADI"," userResponse":" ZAWADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128581318","data":{"timestamp":" 947128581317"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f824b62e-f6d6-4642-bcf2-52fca3967479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZEZE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZEZE"," userResponse":" ZEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128583967","data":{"timestamp":" 947128583967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f824b62e-f6d6-4642-bcf2-52fca3967479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZEZE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZEZE"," userResponse":" ZEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128585606","data":{"timestamp":" 947128585605"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f824b62e-f6d6-4642-bcf2-52fca3967479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZULIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZULIA"," userResponse":" ZULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128588172","data":{"timestamp":" 947128588171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f824b62e-f6d6-4642-bcf2-52fca3967479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZULIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZULIA"," userResponse":" ZULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128589808","data":{"timestamp":" 947128589807"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f824b62e-f6d6-4642-bcf2-52fca3967479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZURI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128592340","data":{"timestamp":" 947128592340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f824b62e-f6d6-4642-bcf2-52fca3967479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZURI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128593941","data":{"timestamp":" 947128593940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f824b62e-f6d6-4642-bcf2-52fca3967479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZIZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIZI"," userResponse":" ZIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128596529","data":{"timestamp":" 947128596528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f824b62e-f6d6-4642-bcf2-52fca3967479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZIZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIZI"," userResponse":" ZIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128598167","data":{"timestamp":" 947128598166"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f824b62e-f6d6-4642-bcf2-52fca3967479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZABIBU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZABIBU"," userResponse":" ZABIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128601075","data":{"timestamp":" 947128601075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f824b62e-f6d6-4642-bcf2-52fca3967479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZABIBU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZABIBU"," userResponse":" ZABIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128603109","data":{"timestamp":" 947128603107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f824b62e-f6d6-4642-bcf2-52fca3967479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ZABIBU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128603226","data":{"timestamp":" 947128603226"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f824b62e-f6d6-4642-bcf2-52fca3967479"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZABIBU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZABIBU"," userResponse":" ZABIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128618931","data":{"timestamp":" 947128618930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 9f9ab092-626a-4b18-b03a-23b8f94f409c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZIWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" ZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128621528","data":{"timestamp":" 947128621528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 9f9ab092-626a-4b18-b03a-23b8f94f409c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZIWA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIWA"," userResponse":" ZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128623143","data":{"timestamp":" 947128623142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 9f9ab092-626a-4b18-b03a-23b8f94f409c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZIPU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128625654","data":{"timestamp":" 947128625653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 9f9ab092-626a-4b18-b03a-23b8f94f409c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZIPU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128627260","data":{"timestamp":" 947128627259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 9f9ab092-626a-4b18-b03a-23b8f94f409c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZAIDI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128629876","data":{"timestamp":" 947128629876"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 9f9ab092-626a-4b18-b03a-23b8f94f409c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZAIDI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128631472","data":{"timestamp":" 947128631471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 9f9ab092-626a-4b18-b03a-23b8f94f409c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZAWADI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAWADI"," userResponse":" ZAWADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128634277","data":{"timestamp":" 947128634276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 9f9ab092-626a-4b18-b03a-23b8f94f409c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZAWADI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAWADI"," userResponse":" ZAWADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128635917","data":{"timestamp":" 947128635916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 9f9ab092-626a-4b18-b03a-23b8f94f409c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZEZE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZEZE"," userResponse":" ZEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128638323","data":{"timestamp":" 947128638323"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 9f9ab092-626a-4b18-b03a-23b8f94f409c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZEZE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZEZE"," userResponse":" ZEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128639953","data":{"timestamp":" 947128639952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 9f9ab092-626a-4b18-b03a-23b8f94f409c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZULIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZULIA"," userResponse":" ZULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128642533","data":{"timestamp":" 947128642532"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 9f9ab092-626a-4b18-b03a-23b8f94f409c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZULIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZULIA"," userResponse":" ZULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128644172","data":{"timestamp":" 947128644172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 9f9ab092-626a-4b18-b03a-23b8f94f409c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZURI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128646686","data":{"timestamp":" 947128646685"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 9f9ab092-626a-4b18-b03a-23b8f94f409c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZURI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" ZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128648296","data":{"timestamp":" 947128648295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 9f9ab092-626a-4b18-b03a-23b8f94f409c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZIZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIZI"," userResponse":" ZIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128650860","data":{"timestamp":" 947128650860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 9f9ab092-626a-4b18-b03a-23b8f94f409c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZIZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIZI"," userResponse":" ZIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128652475","data":{"timestamp":" 947128652474"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 9f9ab092-626a-4b18-b03a-23b8f94f409c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZABIBU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZABIBU"," userResponse":" ZABIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128655182","data":{"timestamp":" 947128655181"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 9f9ab092-626a-4b18-b03a-23b8f94f409c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZABIBU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZABIBU"," userResponse":" ZABIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128657209","data":{"timestamp":" 947128657207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 9f9ab092-626a-4b18-b03a-23b8f94f409c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ZABIBU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128657331","data":{"timestamp":" 947128657331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 9f9ab092-626a-4b18-b03a-23b8f94f409c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.39"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ZABIBU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZABIBU"," userResponse":" ZABIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128684608","data":{"timestamp":" 947128684608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" c1452e32-6e3a-4765-9926-829039ac8f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-CH-K"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128702980","data":{"timestamp":" 947128702979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" c1452e32-6e3a-4765-9926-829039ac8f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_D-Y-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128716932","data":{"timestamp":" 947128716931"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" c1452e32-6e3a-4765-9926-829039ac8f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-O-I"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128721426","data":{"timestamp":" 947128721426"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" c1452e32-6e3a-4765-9926-829039ac8f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Y-E-Z"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128731165","data":{"timestamp":" 947128731165"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" c1452e32-6e3a-4765-9926-829039ac8f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Y-E-Z"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128737391","data":{"timestamp":" 947128737391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" c1452e32-6e3a-4765-9926-829039ac8f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_V-A-Z"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128742109","data":{"timestamp":" 947128742109"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" c1452e32-6e3a-4765-9926-829039ac8f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-A-E"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128746809","data":{"timestamp":" 947128746809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" c1452e32-6e3a-4765-9926-829039ac8f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_E-Z-H"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128752917","data":{"timestamp":" 947128752916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" c1452e32-6e3a-4765-9926-829039ac8f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-W-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128757378","data":{"timestamp":" 947128757377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" c1452e32-6e3a-4765-9926-829039ac8f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_F-Z-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128762649","data":{"timestamp":" 947128762649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" c1452e32-6e3a-4765-9926-829039ac8f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-K-W"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128768437","data":{"timestamp":" 947128768434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" c1452e32-6e3a-4765-9926-829039ac8f35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.73"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-K-W"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128836766","data":{"timestamp":" 947128836765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 7537e738-6bd3-46fa-bd79-1194da3f9b15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_F-K-Z"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128843744","data":{"timestamp":" 947128843744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 7537e738-6bd3-46fa-bd79-1194da3f9b15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_B-Z-I"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128847665","data":{"timestamp":" 947128847665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 7537e738-6bd3-46fa-bd79-1194da3f9b15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_L-V-Z"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128852582","data":{"timestamp":" 947128852582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 7537e738-6bd3-46fa-bd79-1194da3f9b15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-Y-A"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128857439","data":{"timestamp":" 947128857439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 7537e738-6bd3-46fa-bd79-1194da3f9b15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-U-W"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128870436","data":{"timestamp":" 947128870436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 7537e738-6bd3-46fa-bd79-1194da3f9b15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_CH-Z-D"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128874569","data":{"timestamp":" 947128874569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 7537e738-6bd3-46fa-bd79-1194da3f9b15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_A-CH-Z"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128889662","data":{"timestamp":" 947128889661"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 7537e738-6bd3-46fa-bd79-1194da3f9b15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_Z-U-F"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128895049","data":{"timestamp":" 947128895049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 7537e738-6bd3-46fa-bd79-1194da3f9b15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_CH-Z-G"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128899019","data":{"timestamp":" 947128899019"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 7537e738-6bd3-46fa-bd79-1194da3f9b15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_H-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128904801","data":{"timestamp":" 947128904799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 7537e738-6bd3-46fa-bd79-1194da3f9b15"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.74"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_H-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128945077","data":{"timestamp":" 947128945076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 4f43ec1f-98e6-4a9f-8562-e0959578c7da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128947498","data":{"timestamp":" 947128947497"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 4f43ec1f-98e6-4a9f-8562-e0959578c7da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128949090","data":{"timestamp":" 947128949089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 4f43ec1f-98e6-4a9f-8562-e0959578c7da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128952648","data":{"timestamp":" 947128952647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 4f43ec1f-98e6-4a9f-8562-e0959578c7da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128954240","data":{"timestamp":" 947128954240"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 4f43ec1f-98e6-4a9f-8562-e0959578c7da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128959276","data":{"timestamp":" 947128959276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 4f43ec1f-98e6-4a9f-8562-e0959578c7da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128959439","data":{"timestamp":" 947128959438"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 4f43ec1f-98e6-4a9f-8562-e0959578c7da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128959510","data":{"timestamp":" 947128959510"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 4f43ec1f-98e6-4a9f-8562-e0959578c7da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128983015","data":{"timestamp":" 947128983014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 00a45f95-bc4c-4603-a912-f10aefb4f674"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128983021","data":{"timestamp":" 947128983021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 00a45f95-bc4c-4603-a912-f10aefb4f674"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947128983082","data":{"timestamp":" 947128983082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 00a45f95-bc4c-4603-a912-f10aefb4f674"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129014871","data":{"timestamp":" 947129014871"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" d2f227c0-a991-44fa-a827-df0603baf9e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129027620","data":{"timestamp":" 947129027620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" d2f227c0-a991-44fa-a827-df0603baf9e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129091937","data":{"timestamp":" 947129091937"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" d2f227c0-a991-44fa-a827-df0603baf9e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129104637","data":{"timestamp":" 947129104636"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" d2f227c0-a991-44fa-a827-df0603baf9e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129118240","data":{"timestamp":" 947129118240"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" d2f227c0-a991-44fa-a827-df0603baf9e1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_24"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129178108","data":{"timestamp":" 947129178108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129190882","data":{"timestamp":" 947129190882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_B"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129201384","data":{"timestamp":" 947129201384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" C"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129205850","data":{"timestamp":" 947129205850"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129217228","data":{"timestamp":" 947129217227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129228075","data":{"timestamp":" 947129228075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129236776","data":{"timestamp":" 947129236776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129248650","data":{"timestamp":" 947129248650"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_F"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129259709","data":{"timestamp":" 947129259709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_G"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129271919","data":{"timestamp":" 947129271919"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_H"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129282545","data":{"timestamp":" 947129282545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_I"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129293550","data":{"timestamp":" 947129293549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129305185","data":{"timestamp":" 947129305185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129315838","data":{"timestamp":" 947129315838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129328140","data":{"timestamp":" 947129328140"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_M"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129340034","data":{"timestamp":" 947129340034"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_N"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129351255","data":{"timestamp":" 947129351255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129362602","data":{"timestamp":" 947129362602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_P"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129374552","data":{"timestamp":" 947129374552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_R"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129385528","data":{"timestamp":" 947129385527"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129396227","data":{"timestamp":" 947129396227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129407534","data":{"timestamp":" 947129407534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129418299","data":{"timestamp":" 947129418299"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_V"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129431131","data":{"timestamp":" 947129431131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_W"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129441428","data":{"timestamp":" 947129441428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129449888","data":{"timestamp":" 947129449888"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129460552","data":{"timestamp":" 947129460552"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129475001","data":{"timestamp":" 947129474999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" ba8cbd43-a3df-4af7-ae79-4a8fced6b334"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129514183","data":{"timestamp":" 947129514183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129525452","data":{"timestamp":" 947129525452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_B"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129534685","data":{"timestamp":" 947129534685"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" C"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129538146","data":{"timestamp":" 947129538146"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129549459","data":{"timestamp":" 947129549459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129560598","data":{"timestamp":" 947129560598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129571891","data":{"timestamp":" 947129571890"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_F"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129583938","data":{"timestamp":" 947129583938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_G"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129594980","data":{"timestamp":" 947129594980"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_H"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129615875","data":{"timestamp":" 947129615875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_I"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129628675","data":{"timestamp":" 947129628675"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129635792","data":{"timestamp":" 947129635792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129645203","data":{"timestamp":" 947129645203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129656373","data":{"timestamp":" 947129656373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129669132","data":{"timestamp":" 947129669132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129680249","data":{"timestamp":" 947129680249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129687692","data":{"timestamp":" 947129687692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129696963","data":{"timestamp":" 947129696962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129704131","data":{"timestamp":" 947129704131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129715212","data":{"timestamp":" 947129715212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_M"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129724236","data":{"timestamp":" 947129724236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_M"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129736701","data":{"timestamp":" 947129736701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_N"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129745538","data":{"timestamp":" 947129745538"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_N"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129756396","data":{"timestamp":" 947129756396"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129765186","data":{"timestamp":" 947129765186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129776008","data":{"timestamp":" 947129776008"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_P"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129787266","data":{"timestamp":" 947129787266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_R"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129797998","data":{"timestamp":" 947129797997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129810672","data":{"timestamp":" 947129810671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129819805","data":{"timestamp":" 947129819804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129829263","data":{"timestamp":" 947129829262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129838977","data":{"timestamp":" 947129838977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129849194","data":{"timestamp":" 947129849194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_V"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129864503","data":{"timestamp":" 947129864503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_W"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129872774","data":{"timestamp":" 947129872774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_W"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129884374","data":{"timestamp":" 947129884373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_W"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129895004","data":{"timestamp":" 947129895004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129906076","data":{"timestamp":" 947129906076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc:all.asc.A..Z.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129920463","data":{"timestamp":" 947129920461"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" f6f0ea79-87b5-45b1-a708-057d4481e789"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc_all.asc.A..Z.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129967215","data":{"timestamp":" 947129967215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129978950","data":{"timestamp":" 947129978950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_B"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947129998073","data":{"timestamp":" 947129998073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" C"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130006653","data":{"timestamp":" 947130006653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" C"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130010044","data":{"timestamp":" 947130010043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130022321","data":{"timestamp":" 947130022321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130033113","data":{"timestamp":" 947130033113"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130043517","data":{"timestamp":" 947130043517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130055509","data":{"timestamp":" 947130055509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130066129","data":{"timestamp":" 947130066129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_F"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130077000","data":{"timestamp":" 947130077000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_F"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130087444","data":{"timestamp":" 947130087444"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_G"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130099418","data":{"timestamp":" 947130099418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_H"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130108928","data":{"timestamp":" 947130108928"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_I"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130126394","data":{"timestamp":" 947130126393"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130137471","data":{"timestamp":" 947130137471"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130147360","data":{"timestamp":" 947130147359"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130158931","data":{"timestamp":" 947130158931"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_M"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130170290","data":{"timestamp":" 947130170289"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_N"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130208739","data":{"timestamp":" 947130208739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130219969","data":{"timestamp":" 947130219969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_P"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130230204","data":{"timestamp":" 947130230204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_R"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130241915","data":{"timestamp":" 947130241915"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_R"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130254329","data":{"timestamp":" 947130254329"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_R"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130264463","data":{"timestamp":" 947130264463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130275262","data":{"timestamp":" 947130275261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130286215","data":{"timestamp":" 947130286215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130296984","data":{"timestamp":" 947130296984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_V"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130308740","data":{"timestamp":" 947130308740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_W"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130319308","data":{"timestamp":" 947130319307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_W"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130331168","data":{"timestamp":" 947130331168"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_W"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130352749","data":{"timestamp":" 947130352749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_W"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130363920","data":{"timestamp":" 947130363920"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130371904","data":{"timestamp":" 947130371904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130383513","data":{"timestamp":" 947130383513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130394810","data":{"timestamp":" 947130394810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130404968","data":{"timestamp":" 947130404968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130415523","data":{"timestamp":" 947130415523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.uc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130429539","data":{"timestamp":" 947130429537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" b93b9072-6a97-4a05-a5da-a6f8dcf7f129"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.uc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130460729","data":{"timestamp":" 947130460729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Y_R_CH"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130467394","data":{"timestamp":" 947130467394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_G_A_L"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130474009","data":{"timestamp":" 947130474008"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_D_O"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130480644","data":{"timestamp":" 947130480644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_B_U_A"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130487270","data":{"timestamp":" 947130487270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_M_H_D"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130493930","data":{"timestamp":" 947130493929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_M_U"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130500580","data":{"timestamp":" 947130500580"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Z_Y_E"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130507198","data":{"timestamp":" 947130507197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_G_A_L"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130513839","data":{"timestamp":" 947130513839"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_U_W"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130520486","data":{"timestamp":" 947130520486"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_U_N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130531303","data":{"timestamp":" 947130531302"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_T_W"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130537955","data":{"timestamp":" 947130537955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_B_U_A"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130544606","data":{"timestamp":" 947130544603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_M_W_K"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130551261","data":{"timestamp":" 947130551261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_I_U_N"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130557945","data":{"timestamp":" 947130557945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_H_W_O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130564597","data":{"timestamp":" 947130564597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_F_P_O"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130571213","data":{"timestamp":" 947130571212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_G_A_L"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130577868","data":{"timestamp":" 947130577867"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_V_J_S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130584520","data":{"timestamp":" 947130584520"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_U_W"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130591157","data":{"timestamp":" 947130591156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_U_F_E"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130601984","data":{"timestamp":" 947130601984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_V_R"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130608637","data":{"timestamp":" 947130608636"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_J_I_W"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130615256","data":{"timestamp":" 947130615255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Z_Y_E"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130621886","data":{"timestamp":" 947130621885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_D_M_Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130629324","data":{"timestamp":" 947130629324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_D_M_Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947130637222","data":{"timestamp":" 947130637222"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_061419"," gameId":" 1551867e-8158-4be5-a7f4-de213ebde24a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.24.asc.say.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_D_M_Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}